(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Let's get out of here.
-Follow me.
-Okay.
-Wait!
-Where are you?
Where are we going right now?
The gym!
-Se-ah and Ha-joon are in the gym.
-Se-ah?
The gym!
I'm blind in one eye, so I'm a bit slow.
Hey, wait up!
Na-ri.
Hey, Lim Na-ri.
-How could you?
-Se-ah, watch out!
Ha-joon!
-Which way?
-Not that way!
-Go left!
-Where?
Go!
-Up there?
-Go!
Ha-joon, are you okay?
Lim Na-ri, are you insane?
I saw your wish video!
-Are you threatening me?
-No.
I'm trying to help you.
You had no idea
Girigo would actually grant your wish.
A wish you only made as a joke
got your friend killed.
I know exactly how that feels.
You're lonely and scared right now.
I felt the same way
after I made my wish, Na-ri.
Ha-joon's sister can help us.
She helped me when I started acting weird.
So, Na-ri…
put that thing down.
Okay?
Na-ri.
-Don't go!
-Why not?
That's not a human.
Na-ri!
IF WISHES COULD KILL
Please.
Stop.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Geon-woo, what happened to your neck?
Se-ah.
I'm all good, thanks to you.
So from now on,
stop worrying about me
and look after yourself first, okay?
Kids, where's a hospital nearby?
The closest one.
My aunt's hospital.
Call your aunt. Let's head there now.
Ha-joon's arm might be broken.
They ran away from there.
How could they possibly go back?
It should be okay
as long as we don't go in.
He's right, Ha-joon.
You two look badly hurt.
Let's get to the hospital.
SEORIN HOSPITAL
-Yeah?
-Why aren't you getting out?
I'm only slightly hurt. I'll be fine.
Go on without me.
Slightly hurt? You're badly hurt.
Go inside and get treated properly.
Worried about your brother-in-law?
Stop talking nonsense. Get out now.
All right.
-That hurts!
-Sorry, my bad.
-Are you okay?
-Keep your distance.
What's with you? That's gross!
They look like family. It's nice.
Right?
Yeah.
Just a moment, please.
I'll quickly check
if you can be discharged.
-Thank you.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Hey, stop it.
-This made me lose my sense of distance.
Haetsal sure is going to chew us out.
You're worried about that, not my arm.
That's why you stayed in the car.
Why would you say that? That hurts.
I had my reasons
for not getting out of the car.
What? What were they?
When a man and a woman are alone
in a car late at night…
Jesus, you and your nonsense.
I'm only worried
your one-sided crush will end miserably.
Too bad you hurt your eye
instead of your mouth.
Nope.
I guess it's good I hurt my eye.
Whatever, man.
Brother-in-law.
The power dwelling in Haetsal
is beyond what a human body can endure.
So we have to keep suppressing that power,
using the divine spirit's ability
to see it.
But what if I could
also see that power,
just like the divine spirit?
When you said
it was good you hurt your eye…
Since I hurt my eye, I can see spirits.
Haetsal's power is based on spirit,
so I should see it, right?
Does this mean Ha-young will be able
to go outside like she used to?
It might take some time to figure out how,
but I promise I'll get her out.
I can get her out.
You mean it, brother-in-law? Really?
-Brother-in-law?
-Never said that.
That's what you called me.
Why "brother-in-law" all of a sudden?
I didn't call you that.
Stay back. It's hot.
Slow down.
Your brother-in-law with the injured eye
can't keep up.
I gotta hurry, you know?
If I'm going to see Ha-young,
I need to find the location first.
Right, brother-in-law?
Let's go.
SEORIN HOSPITAL
Are these all wish videos?
Yeah.
If our guess is correct,
then this one, being the first posted,
must have been the wish video
that made the app a curse.
I'll play it now.
Okay.
Wondering what this crazy bitch is up to?
I'll make the wish
just the way you told me.
My wish is
for all of you to die.
I truly wish every one of you
would just drop dead.
That's my wish.
No doubt about it.
Hyeong-wook and Do Hye-ryung…
both died in the same way.
The phone that filmed this…
is the red phone.
HAEJU INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX
I got the location.
Okay. Let's go.
Do Hye-ryung filmed her wish video
at the marked location.
You all remember the rainbow window
in the Polaroid photo, right?
Yeah.
Find the building with that window.
The red phone is definitely
where that window is, right?
It will definitely be there.
Remember.
Only you can get it out of there.
You're the only one
connected to both the red phone and me.
Don't worry, Se-ah.
As long as you have the thread,
they can't touch you.
But what's this rainbow window?
Here. Take a look and give it to Se-ah.
-Se-ah, hold onto that.
-Okay.
So all we have to do
is find that red phone thing
and bring it to Ha-young
for Se-ah to be completely okay, right?
Of course.
Geon-woo and Na-ri
will also go back to normal, right?
Yeah.
If we find the maehyung,
we should be able to save everyone cursed.
Oh, that's right.
Na-ri and I found something
when we went into the nurse's office.
Laceration on the neck.
"Kwon Si-won"?
The shaman's child who went to Baekun?
Brother-in-law, take a picture of this
and send it to your sister.
Okay.
GIRIGO
MAKE A WISH
Fuck you, Do Hye-ryung!
Let Do Hye-ryung's curse repeat itself.
YOUR WISH HAS BEEN GRANTED
HAEJU INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX
Ten minutes out.
Okay.
Don't be scared.
I'm here with you guys.
BAEKUN-DONG
3 KM, 7 MINUTES
Sure is creepy here.
The route cannot be found.
What?
Straight ahead, right?
Yes, straight ahead. Keep going.
-Huh? What's wrong with this thing?
-What is it?
My phone's GPS isn't working either.
I think we turn right around here.
What is this?
Hold on tight!
Are you okay?
-Are you guys okay?
-Yes, I think we're okay.
This is a nasty one.
No!
Remember.
Only you can get it out of there.
You're the only one
connected to both the red phone and me.
Unbind our wrongs
and ward off all ill-omened fate.
Hey! Se-ah! Don't open the door!
Don't open the door! No!
Brother-in-law.
Oh God! Brother-in-law!
It's okay.
No, don't say anything!
You have to do it.
Only you can do this.
Find the red phone, so we
can hurry back to Haetsal.
It's okay. Don't cry.
Brother-in-law, the knife…
Okay.
Don't talk, okay?
Here's the knife.
Geon-woo.
When the spirit compass starts spinning,
it means that those things
from the other side are nearby.
So you need to keep an eye on that.
Keep Se-ah safe.
Okay.
I'll protect her.
Go. Hurry.
Go, quick.
Se-ah, let's go.
Please.
Oh God. Brother-in-law.
Oh, 119.
It's okay.
Did the kids leave?
Yeah, they left.
Okay, then I need to rest now.
Stop talking and stay with me!
Okay.
Brother-in-law.
Yeah.
Go to your sister. Go to Haetsal.
What are you talking about?
I called 119. Hang in there!
Brother-in-law,
you said you'd get my sister out of there!
So don't die on me!
"Brother-in-law."
-Yes, brother-in-law.
-"Brother-in-law."
Brother-in-law.
No, you can't die.
Se-ah!
Look at this.
This way, right?
Yeah.
This window.
We just need to find it.
Let's go.
The rainbow window.
Jesus.
Damn it.
Not here, I think.
Not here either.
Se-ah.
Let me see that Polaroid photo again.
Okay.
We don't have much time.
Let's split up and look for it.
-Okay.
-I'll go this way and look for it.
Be careful.
You too.
Penetrating lower-right abdominal wound.
Heavy bleeding.
You need to live, brother-in-law.
Expect heavy bleeding. Prep a transfusion.
I'll remove it now.
Suction!
Not this window either.
Not this one either.
Geon-woo! I found it!
Huh? You found it?
You found it? Where?
Ha-young.
Brother-in-law is in the operating room.
He was trying to protect us.
No, Ha-joon. Don't think like that.
It's not your fault,
and the surgery will go well.
I'll go over there.
Okay.
These stairs are broken.
Geon-woo, over here!
Se-ah, be careful.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hey.
Hold on. I'll go first.
No, it's okay.
I'll go first.
No other choice.
What are you doing? Huh? It's dangerous.
What are you doing?
Hey, you're gonna jump?
It's barely a gap.
Still, let me jump across instead.
I'm the only one who can find the phone.
Don't worry.
Se-ah, are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Geon-woo, it's dangerous. Stay there.
What are you saying?
I'm coming across too.
Geon-woo.
I'm really okay.
I'll check and be right back.
Se-ah.
Na-ri.
Na-ri!
Se-ah!
Lim Na-ri!
You're not going anywhere.
I won't let you go.
Please!
Come to your senses!
Close your eyes
and take a moment to think.
"The whole world is the mat."
"I can do this."
Picture that,
and when you open your eyes,
run like crazy and jump.
I can do this.
Na-ri.
Na…
Na-ri, it's you, right?
How did we end up like this?
Na-ri.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go back together.
Okay?
No.
I told you we can't get out of here.
I told you I won't let you go.
No!
Se-ah!
Se-ah, snap out of it!
Se-ah.
Se-ah!
No.
Se-ah…
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang